Kontakt

www.linkedin.com/in/rodecharlotte (LinkedIn)

Top-Kenntnisse

Marketing Communications
Strategy
Marketing

Languages

German (Native or Bilingual) French (Elementary) Englisch (Full Professional)

Charlotte Rode

Account Manager at fischerAppelt

Hamburg und Umgebung

Zusammenfassung

Dynamic and reliable Marketing and Public Relations professional with 5+ years experience on working with clients on their Marketing and PR strategies in the fashion and lifestyle industry. Commended for my strong analytical and communicative skills as well as excellent planning and organizational capabilities with the ability to balance multiple projects and tasks under tight deadlines.

Berufserfahrung

fischerAppelt

5 Jahre 7 Monate

Account Manager Januar 2018 - Present (4 Jahre 4 Monate)

Hamburg Area, Germany

Berater

Oktober 2016 - Dezember 2017 (1 Jahr 3 Monate)

Hamburg

BNS, Brand New Solutions Senior Account Executive April 2016 - September 2016 (6 Monate) Sydney und Umgebung, Australien

Network Public Relations

2 Jahre 1 Monat

Junior Account Manager März 2015 - September 2015 (7 Monate)

Network Public Relations was established in Hamburg in 1997 and is specialized in the communication of fashion, lifestyle and beauty brands within the German-speaking markets. Developing and realizing efficient PR strategies as well as establishing and consolidating brands and products in the luxury and premium segment are key competencies of the agency.

PR Assistant

Oktober 2014 - März 2015 (6 Monate)

Trainee

September 2013 - Oktober 2014 (1 Jahr 2 Monate)

Schoeller & von Rehlingen Public Relations Intern März 2013 - Juni 2013 (4 Monate)

Closed GmbH

Sales Intern

Januar 2013 - März 2013 (3 Monate)

OHMS CONSULTING

Administration and Recruitment Fashion and Lifestyle Intern April 2012 - Dezember 2012 (9 Monate)

WARSTEINER Brauerei Haus Cramer Management Gmbh Brand Marketing Intern August 2011 - September 2011 (2 Monate)

Warstein, Germany

Cushman & Wakefield Intern Real Estate Management März 2010 - April 2010 (2 Monate)

BCI Asia

Intern Research Department September 2009 - Oktober 2009 (2 Monate)

Ausbildung

Westfälische Wilhelms-Universität Münster Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.), Business Administration and Management, General · (2009 - 2012)

Kapaun Mount Carmel

High School Year · (2005 - 2006)